<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Noah Glaser</title><link>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Noah Glaser</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.codingwithnoah.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ElectroBlocks</title><link>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/electroblocks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/electroblocks/</guid><description>An Arduino IDE that uses Blockly and has a built-in playback simulator. It&amp;rsquo;s like video editing, but for code. It also allows you to upload code directly to the Arduino board.</description></item><item><title>Loan Calculator</title><link>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/loancalculator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/loancalculator/</guid><description>This is simple loan calculator. It&amp;rsquo;s ad free and will calculate the interest, total paid and monthly payments. If you have any questions feel free to email me at glaserpower [@] gmail.com</description></item><item><title>Space Jumper</title><link>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/spacejumper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/spacejumper/</guid><description>This is a space jumper game built in a Phaser 3 game engine. It uses animations, physics, and sprite groups. The assets are from kenny.nl.</description></item><item><title>Svelte Arduino LED Matrix</title><link>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/ledmatrix/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/ledmatrix/</guid><description>This website allows you to control and LED matrix directly from the browser. It uses experimental serial api to do this. It was built using svelte framework.</description></item><item><title>Svelte Prism NPM Package</title><link>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/svelte-prismjs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/projects/svelte-prismjs/</guid><description>This npm package allows you integrate prismjs into a svelte website. Prismjs is a library for displaying code on webpages. I have example repositories showing how to use it with Sapper and Routify. You can find out more by clicking hte github link. I am always open for pull requests. :)</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy
Noah Glaser built the Loan Calculator Ad Free app as an Open Source app. This SERVICE is provided by Noah Glaser at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.codingwithnoah.com/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;#34;HTML&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;JSON&amp;#34;] Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description></item></channel></rss>